Leaving us hanging.
She's building suspense. Where is she?
- I think she's arrived.
- Has she?
What?
MARU (28)
HOST/PRESIDENT
Damn, lady… Damn.
RYOPI (29)
BAR OWNER
MIMI (29)
OSAKA - HOSTESS
Um, nice to meet you.
Um, my name is Mimina Ito.
Well, I work at a hostess bar
in Kitashinchi, Osaka.
Bro…
She's something.
RINRIN (20)
HOSTESS
RUNE (28)
RAPPER/BUSINESS OWNER
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
SHARAN (21)
LOUNGE HOSTESS
SARA (26)
NAIL ARTIST
KAZUMA (26)
PART-TIMER
My nickname is Mimi.
I'm glad to be here with you all.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- Good to see you. It's been a while.
- It's been a while.
- Yes, excuse me. Good morning.
- He's a super familiar face.
- Do you know each other?
- I'm used to serving her like a slave.
No, no, no.
It was shocking, I didn't expect
someone I knew to show up just like that.
It's so weird 'cause we both work…
right in the Kitashinchi area.
I mean, it's not like
we're super close friends or anything.
But she does come by my bar for drinks
with her coworkers sometimes.
It totally caught me off guard.
First impression? Uh…
I definitely thought she's gorgeous.
- Can't blame him for that response.
- Fair.
I was like, "Okay, I'm ready
to go all out for her,"
I was back in that first-day mindset.
- Whoa.
- Oh!
It flipped a switch in my head.
I'm gonna go for it.
She's so pretty.
God, she's hot.
So yeah, I like her already.
NAGANO
- He's head over heels.
- Tai-chan's already in!
- That was fast.
- Too fast!
He doesn't even know her at all!
Just go home.
No, I'm not going home. I just got here.
- We don't need you here.
- No.
- You should go.
- Seriously, no.
Do you want love?
Well, I think I can.
Why are you here?
What am I here for?
Well, I'm here to fall in love.
We don't need you.
- Go home.
- You go home.
- No, you go home.
- Why?
- Get the hell out!
- Hey, shut up, ugly.
Get out. You're the ugly one.
- I can't deal with you.
- Get out now.
- So lame.
- Who is?
Don't mess with me.
- Oh yikes, this is getting scary.
- It's a real showdown.
Get out. I mean it.
Okay, why don't you sit down for now?
- What?
- Why don't you sit down?
- Am I allowed to?
- Why wouldn't you be?
Great, I get to sit next to you.
Sorry about that.
That was sassy.
Yeah she's already showing her fiery side.
No kidding.
Attention, ladies.
Please make a nice welcome dinner
for the new transfer student,
so she can feel more at home.
And to our transfer student,
since you joined late,
please spend some time
with the guys in the living room.
Get to know them better.
Copy that.
That's hilarious.
- Wanna head out?
- Yeah, living room?
- Should we?
- Let's get out of here.
I'll show you where it is.
- Huh?
- I can show you. I got you.
- What do they call you here?
- Oh, just Ryopi.
You're pissed at Ryopi.
- You pissed at him now?
- Whatever, I don't care.
No point in telling him.
Later. We'll talk later.
- Huh?
- Talk to you later.
Oh, Kazuma is so nice.
See y'all later.
- How you doing?
- Sorry?
So let me get this straight.
We're supposed to cook for her?
For that girl?
- That's annoying.
- And…
Ryopi is being so gross.
Like, what is he doing?
Yeah, totally.
She kissed him, right?
Yeah, she did.
It literally happened yesterday.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
They know each other?
They're like, "It's been a while."
Still, why is he all over her like that?
What the hell?
So gross. After yesterday…
with what happened between them. Now this?
- It's just gross.
- I seriously don't give a shit.
For real.
- Whoa, that totally gave me the ick.
- I know, right? Those two are crazy.
I got the ick too.
Just killed my feelings for him.
Hmm…
Geez, guys,
she literally just introduced herself!
What did Mimi even do to deserve this?
I'm a little worried
they might poison her food.
Yikes. I'm on edge already.
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RUGGED APPRENTICE TATTOO ARTIST
DRAWN TO TATTOOS' SEX APPEAL
KAZUMA
KABUKICHO HOST BOSS
WHO WANTS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT LOVE
MARU
IBARAKI HOSTESS WITH A BIKE CREW
LOOKING FOR A HUSBAND
AYACHERU
GYARU HOSTESS FROM MIYAGI
A TSUNDERE WHO HATES TO LOSE
RINRIN
KITASHINCHI BAR OWNER
WHO'S ALL ABOUT THE VIBES
RYOPI
WILD OKINAWAN NAIL ARTIST
WITH A PHOENIX ON HER BACK
SARA
FUKUSHIMA HOSTESS
WHO CHARGES INTO LOVE HEAD-FIRST
SHARAN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
EDOGAWA RAPPER
SEEKING LOVE WITH HONOR
RUNE
KITASHINCHI'S NO.1 HOSTESS
BLEEDING BIG-SIS ENERGY
MIMI
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
Come on in.
After you, boys. Go ahead.
- Welcome.
- What?
- After you. Come in.
- Wow, this place is so cute!
It's totally retro!
- Check out the pool table.
- Yeah. Amazing.
- Where we supposed to sit?
- Wherever you want.
- Go right ahead.
- I'll sit here.
What do we do? Show her the ropes?
Or, like, introduce ourselves?
Yeah, that's better.
Yeah, let's do it. Introduce yourselves.
So, I'm from Kanagawa Prefecture,
and I'm 26.
- Oh, 26.
- Yep, and my name is Kazuma.
- It's a pleasure.
- Great. Nice to meet you.
- I'm Rune.
- Rune?
- Rune, that's right.
- Wow, cool.
- And I'm 28. Nice to meet you.
- Ah, nice to meet you.
Oh, I'm Maru.
I'm the representative director
of a host club in Kabukicho.
- And I'm 28 too. Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, likewise.
I'm Tai-chan.
I'm 22, and I work as a hairstylist.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah, you too.
Wow, we're all different ages.
- We're the oldest ones here.
- That's true.
Actually, Mimi,
you're already like a pretty major
celebrity in the nightlife scene, right?
Around hostess clubs? Maybe a little.
I've definitely heard of you before.
I think the girls were asking earlier too.
Are you here to find love or--
- Oh, for sure.
- Cool.
The thing is,
a lot of the men around me at work
are usually a little higher in age range.
- They're like 40--
- Like middle age?
Yeah, exactly.
Most of my customers are over 45.
So I don't really get to talk
to people my own age very much.
Hmm…
Yeah, it's hard to surround myself
with people in my age group.
So being here is important.
I came because
I really want to be in a normal
romantic relationship.
- Yeah.
- Is there a certain type of guy you like?
Well, I want a guy
who's kind and is true to his word.
Once he decides to do something,
I want him to see it through.
So, yeah, that's… That's what
I'm looking for in a man, I guess.
True to his word, and kind. Got it.
The other thing is, given the set-up here,
I feel like things could get messy
between the girls.
So I want to see
how the guys step in and support me.
It's a good way to see
how much of a man you are.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh.
That makes sense.
- Wow.
- Whoa, I like that!
- She's something.
- She really is.
I'm not in the mood to cook.
Honestly, I kept thinking,
"Ryopi, stop it." For real.
- I know. That was messed up.
- He's messed up.
I was like, "Knock it off."
Like, "Why are you sucking up to her?"
I feel like I saw
a different side of Kazuma.
I know, right? Right? He's surprisingly--
He said, "I get it, let's talk later."
- Really?
- Yeah.
So she's talking to the guys right now?
Yeah, in the living room.
- In there?
- Yeah, they're chatting.
Gross.
But Tai-chan should be fine, right?
Nah, I doubt it.
He was straight-up…
staring at her.
We better keep
that peeler away from her. She's pissed.
I bet they all like that kind of girl.
All modest and submissive.
- I bet that's Maru's type.
- I guess you're probably right.
- He's a host.
- Right up his alley.
- Who's into her?
- So demure.
Maybe Tai-chan is.
We'll see.
Would you date a younger guy?
I guess,
as long as he's got that mature vibe.
- Didn't sound too convincing.
- Get out!
It's been a while
since I heard a Kansai dialect.
So, you want someone your age?
I don't know. Twenties, I guess.
But someone who's 22 is just…
- I never really meet people that age.
- Don't get the chance?
You said you're usually around
an older crowd.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't feel old.
How about you guys, though?
Do you want to be with someone older,
younger, or the same age?
- I've never thought much about age.
- Yeah, I guess I haven't either.
When it comes
to seriously falling for someone,
I don't think
I've ever really considered age.
Here, you kinda forget about age, right?
- I do! Totally.
- Do you feel younger? Or older?
- Definitely not old. I feel younger.
- Interesting.
Very young vibe.
I wonder if I'll fit in.
- I'm sure you will.
- No doubt.
Give it a couple of days,
and you'll get used to it.
Definitely.
Things might be
a little different with the girls.
It's gonna be a lot harder
to get close to them, don't you think?
Could be scary for you.
I mean, we won't be able
to help you from our room.
- That's true.
- We're separate?
There are always separate bedrooms
for the girls and guys.
I have to be with them.
Honestly, just imagining it
gives me chills, dude.
Yeah.
As a hostess,
I bet she's really good with words.
Like she can butter you up.
She knows how to say just
the right thing to get you to like her.
She must be talking to Ryopi a lot
since they already know each other.
Fine. If they want to talk, let them talk.
Hello, ladies.
- Oh, you scared me!
- Hello.
Come in! Oh wait…
Kazuma is such a nice guy.
Just look at that smile!
- Oh, geez.
- No, it's just, all of you should've come.
All right, what's… what's going on
in here, ladies? Talk to me.
- Like, what's the vibe in here?
- Deadly.
Deadly?
- She's freaky!
- Deadly.
- Someone's gonna die.
- Deadly is crazy.
She's out for blood.
What did you tell the other guys
when you came here?
That I was going to the bathroom.
- For real?
- And how did they react to that?
Actually, I didn't even say that.
I just quietly slipped out, like this.
Sara, you had a lot to say earlier.
Like, "Is this a joke or what?"
Well, yeah, a hostess girl,
someone that famous just showing up here--
- She can't be looking for love.
- Feels like a publicity stunt.
- Is she that famous?
- She's super famous.
- She's a celebrity.
- You never heard of her?
- No.
- That explains it!
- You don't know her?
- No. Does everyone know her but me?
A celebrity hostess
just showed up out of nowhere?
- So, what's the vibe like over there?
- They look like they're having fun?
Just normal. They're just chatting.
She doesn't know much about this place,
like when we first got here, so…
Wait, who's, like, excited?
Excited? Geez, I dunno.
I wouldn't say they're excited, but…
Maru is talking to her a lot.
What?
I knew it'd be Maru!
We totally called it in here.
Wait, really? You called like…
who would talk to her?
We said that it would be Maru or Rune.
Well, we're a little afraid that…
I mean, when we're all together…
things will be fine,
but when it's time to go to sleep
- and you all go to the girls' room…
- You're worried?
Just wondering what the vibe will be.
So you're looking out for everyone.
- For all of us girls. Is that it?
- That's so sweet.
- Seriously, you're really sweet.
- I'm not "worried" really.
It's more like… I'm just curious
how it's gonna go in your room.
If it'll be a good atmosphere.
Right.
Well guys, I have to say,
this is interesting.
So, hang on actually,
- I watched Season one…
- Thank you for watching.
- Remember when Amo showed up?
- Yikes. Amo. Yep.
This situation feels
even more tense than that dynamic.
Exactly! Oh my god, no question.
This goes way beyond
"Not the damn water" now.
This is next level.
She threw it.
I guess these ladies are just…
- They like throwing water around.
- They're drawn to it somehow.
Call it a form of self-expression.
Right, it's very cathartic. You get upset
and then, bam! Just like that.
They're either, throwing,
slamming or making a scene.
So true. And my god,
that look on Rinrin's face…
She's an open book.
I haven't made a face like that in 15--
Actually no, in 20 years.
You don't show that face in public.
But Mimi did talk back a little, right?
She was like, "Shut up, ugly."
How do most men…
feel when they see something like that?
Well, some of these guys
have a bad-boy kind of past,
so they might be more attracted to girls
who look like they can take the lead
and fight for what they want.
And the other guys might fall
for the vulnerable ones.
- We have two types.
- Oh, we just have those two?
- I think so.
- Just two?
There's pretty much just two.
Especially with these badass boys around.
I see, okay.
So, having said all that, uh…
Kazuma was being considerate
and went over to the kitchen
for a few minutes to check on the women.
But the other four guys
might actually prefer a woman
who's a little more brash
and willing to stir up some trouble.
Where did Kazuma go?
- No idea.
- The bathroom?
- Really?
- Right.
Or he poked his head into the…
The kitchen?
Oh, right. They're cooking.
So it's the girls' turn tonight.
- Wait, did you guys cook, too?
- Yesterday.
Really? What did you make? I'm curious.
Maru made burgers,
stewed burgers or something.
Wow! Amazing.
- It's my specialty.
- Nice!
That's some bullshit.
What was that stuff you made, Tai-chan?
- What did you make, Tai-chan?
- Bulgogi.
Bulgogi? Delicious!
- Ryopi?
- I made fried rice.
So those three dishes?
Wait, Kazuma made tonjiru.
Wow, so much variety.
But it all came together.
Each of us made something,
and then we all came together.
Before that we…
had a little talk
between the men and women.
And then,
the men kind of cooked as an apology.
We felt bad.
- Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
- You did something wrong?
Well, we sort of…
No, it was more like
we just weren't doing enough.
Like, you weren't trying?
Actually, I definitely
got chewed out the most.
They were like,
"Why aren't you talking more?"
So yeah, they really singled me out.
Really? That's weird.
You seem like such a talker.
- As of today.
- That's 'cause a girl
who's my type showed up today.
So I gotta lay on the charm.
Is he running for office?
The guy's making speeches now.
- Super subtle t-shirt, too. "Sex"!
- Right, I noticed that too.
I'm dying to know
what they're talking about.
They're all still hanging out?
Wait, who?
All the guys.
Yeah, I guess so.
They're probably still talking.
Two, four, six. Hmm…
- Nine. There's more over here.
- We're short.
Oh, okay, good.
Ooh, nice, looks delicious!
Man, they really went all out.
What if some if it
is secretly spicy as hell?
Do we carry these?
- How do we move them?
- Good question.
I'm the representative director.
- Oh, wow.
- So I do both.
I'm a manager and a host.
- Mmm…
- Yep.
- How long you been doing that?
- About two years.
- Oh, okay.
- I've been with the club for ten years.
- The whole time.
- Impressive. He worked his way up.
Ten years is amazing.
- I'm loyal to them.
- Oh, here they are.
- Can you help carry stuff?
- Here they come.
- Here we go.
- Oh, are we bringing the food in here?
Yeah, we'll just go grab the food
from the kitchen and bring it here.
- Is this trash?
- Ah, no… I mean, yeah.
Man, my heart is pounding right now.
- I'm on edge, yikes.
- Yeesh.
Little scary.
- Something smells so good.
- Smells damn good.
- It really does.
- Guess what we made?
It smells incredible.
- Get ready for a feast, boys.
- That looks so good. Oh, man.
- What can I carry?
- Do we have spoons and stuff? Silverware?
- Oh, yeah, over there.
- Should we take those then?
- Like this?
- Mmm.
- I can take another bowl.
- One too many?
Oh, no, this one should go here.
Yeah, I lost count.
Soup goes on the right, doesn't it?
Let's put that here…
and this there.
Whoa, shoot.
Rune has been counting this whole time…
This one could fall.
One, two…
All right, that's good.
It's wet here for some reason.
- There we go.
- We need one more.
- Huh? One, two, three, four…
- I think like four people
- will probably sit on that side.
- Ah, yeah, I got you.
One, two, three, four…
It's fine, it's fine.
Let's just leave them like this for now.
But this is how they should be, right?
- I want a full plate.
- Looks nice.
- I want a small plate.
- This might be too much.
Do we have chopsticks?
We do. Wait. We're missing one pair.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- One pair.
So, where did my food go?
Yeah, we're definitely one short.
- What! Okay. Eat mine.
- No, I'm good, really.
Nine portions?
Where's mine?
What the?
How many did you guys make?
Nine.
- Are they serious?
- Nine portions?
Whoa, whoa, what is this?
Some prison hazing tactic?
It's like they're trying to intimidate
the new guy in the cellblock.
It's getting a little spooky.
Let's divvy some up.
Oh, no, it's okay. I can go make some.
- No, it's okay.
- Seriously, just eat. Go ahead.
Where's mine?
- How much did you make?
- Not enough.
There's no more left in the kitchen.
Is there any rice left?
- Uh, yeah.
- There is?
- Oh, no, Tai-chan, I'm sorry!
- No problem.
- Come on, let's make some.
- Go ahead and start eating.
- I can't eat that much anyway.
- Let's cook.
- No worries. Let's hit the kitchen.
- No, seriously, I feel so bad.
Don't even worry about it.
I mean, how can they
be missing exactly one serving?
Honestly, just forget about it.
Oh, this is enough for me.
There's some here.
What about rice?
No, I'm good.
We're definitely one short.
They screwed up?
Well, we have some left.
There's still a little bit here.
Let's bring this over there.
Wait, what about rice?
You're gonna eat rice, right?
We still have rice too, right?
- Yeah.
- Then this is good.
Seriously, nothing to worry about.
- This is for you, Rune?
- Yeah.
Okay. How much do you want?
- Just a normal portion.
- For real. I'm okay.
Just need a few bites.
- There's plenty here for me.
- You can give her a smaller plate.
- Uh, here.
- Thanks. Sorry about that.
These look delicious.
Was this a mistake?
That there wasn't enough food.
No, it wasn't a mistake.
So you didn't make enough?
We just didn't dish it up.
- Whoa!
- Oh, man!
- Oh, boy, this is not good.
- Not good.
- That's a really low blow.
- Yeah.
Okay, why?
We agreed that the girls would cook
to say "thank you" for our last dinner.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And it was supposed to be a welcome party
but we don't wanna welcome her.
So, it's a way of saying,
"Get it yourself."
But you fixed plates for the guys
as a way to thank us
for cooking yesterday?
Mmm.
Well, honestly…
I really don't like this kind of stuff.
Them leaving her out of the group?
I mean, it's like…
I get how you girls feel
about not wanting to accept her.
But still, the point is
to share a meal as a group,
so we can learn about each other, right?
Don't you think?
So it just seems unnecessary to take
that opportunity away from yourselves.
At first, I thought mine was missing.
I thought it was a joke, which is fine.
But then I noticed
the soup was missing too.
We still have
a lot of time together, you know?
And we have to live together, right?
I don't know how everyone else feels,
but I would really hate it
if someone did this to me.
Look, I've been in her position before,
and I bet a lot of you have too.
I was bullied a lot in elementary school.
Being treated like that drove me crazy.
I hated it so much.
I took ten years of Karate just so
I could beat up the guy who bullied me
and show him I'm not a pushover.
I knew I had to do
something about it myself,
so that's what kept me going.
But now that I'm this age,
I can't do that anymore.
I'm not supposed to throw hands
even if I wanted to.
So, the question is,
how do you deal with it as an adult?
I think we can find a solution.
Oh, and let me say
because I've been bullied myself,
I've never picked on anyone.
If I ever saw someone
about to get beat up,
I'd stand right in front of him
and tell the bullies, "Swing at me first."
"You can beat him up after,
but I'm not going down without a fight."
Has anyone here ever been bullied?
Not a single person?
I was bullied a lot. I don't think
it's anything to be ashamed of.
I don't feel ashamed about it at all.
But I was so bitter, though.
It really pissed me off.
I hated it so much that I felt like
I had to change and improve myself.
That's how I got to where I am today.
But this just reminded me
of how I felt back in elementary school.
Those are tough memories.
This was supposed to be a fun meal…
but it's taken me back to the past.
This totally…
ruined my mood.
Seriously.
Yeah, he's got a point.
You've got to respect his honesty here.
All right. I'll just eat over there.
Sorry. Thank you for cooking.
Sorry, but I don't wanna eat
with these girls tonight.
Wanna come?
It's okay.
Here we go.
I got it.
Hey, I'm sorry for making you
go out of your way.
No, I didn't go out of my way at all.
Don't worry.
Speaking up in that situation was…
I was wondering if I should say something,
but we were about to eat,
so I didn't want
to ruin the mood or feel like crap.
I just don't want to ruin anyone's night.
I really don't. Doesn't matter
if I'm with my partner,
or my family, or just some friends.
You hear them talking trash
and you wanna confront them now,
like at this moment, and I get that.
I get that you wanna beat them up
right now, but it's time to eat.
I think everyone should be
treated equally. At meals, at least.
We should all be able
to share a meal together. For sure.
Ideally, we should share first,
and if we want to fight,
we can fight afterward.
- Deal with it afterward.
- Mmm-hmm.
That makes sense.
But we should at least be able
to eat together.
You're right. Yeah.
And I felt like
they just ruined that idea.
Well, I think he was right. I…
Yeah, I mean, what he said to us
totally made sense to me.
I get that you don't just feel
like welcoming her, though. Like…
if we had a male transfer student,
I wouldn't be all buddy-buddy
with him either.
I think it's fair to feel that way. Yeah.
I guess we expressed it in the wrong way.
Yeah, and some of the things Rune shared
really hit home for me.
I've been bullied, too.
Really, I have. And it sucks.
To be honest, I think you guys
really took the wrong approach here.
If it's just two people
that have a problem facing off
against each other, that's one thing.
But I think it's messed up
how all of you ganged up on her
and ended up doing something like this.
- What should we do?
- If it's chill now,
I think we should get them back in here.
This kinda stuff… I don't think
we want this to go on much longer.
Okay, I'll go check on them.
Wait, I'll go too.
You sure?
Okay. What do you wanna do, ladies?
Yeah, I think I want to apologize.
Me, too.
Rinrin?
I'm on board with what he said.
So, do you want to apologize?
Probably a good idea.
- Let's all go together.
- Yeah.
- This still a reality dating show?
- Yeah, it still is.
It's a reality dating show,
but it has educational value too.
- If the shoe fits.
- Yeah.
Oh, nice, thank you.
Sure.
Wow. Look at this. That board is amazing.
- It's great, right?
- Yeah.
Badly in Love in a nutshell.
- This good?
- Oh, thank you. Yeah.
"I love you."
- Let's eat.
- Great.
Rune.
- Hmm?
- Got a sec?
Come on.
So, um…
about what happened back there,
after what you said, Rune,
we all felt like apologizing.
I think your words hit us all pretty hard.
I mean, I feel like
I really made the wrong decision.
It's your first day, I don't know you yet,
but for some reason,
I was bullying you like that.
I was just being small and petty.
Honestly, I was like, "Why would
a famous person like her even come here?"
"Is she really here to find love?"
That's what I've been wondering.
Doing what we did before we even knew you,
bullying you like that was not right.
And yeah, so…
what Rune said made a lot of sense to me.
We've all had experiences like that.
- I apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry.
- That's okay.
Sorry about that.
I don't know how to say this,
but well, here's the thing…
I was bullied pretty bad
when I was in fourth grade.
Maybe third? Around then.
Because of how I look.
So, when Rune brought that up,
I thought, "Oh, he's right."
- That's how I felt.
- Mmm-hmm.
So, about what we did, all I can say is…
I'm just really sorry.
So, how about…
you come back and join us,
and we can still have dinner together?
As a group.
Wanna do it?
- Let's start the party.
- All right.
- I'll help you carry some stuff.
- All right, cool.
Thank you.
Whose was this again?
- Oh, thanks.
- Hey, Maru, put this there.
- Thanks.
- For Rune.
- Is it hot?
- No, it's not.
Okay, so, for real this time…
- Yep, take two.
- Right, let's eat.
- Okay guys, enjoy.
- Thanks guys.
- Let's do this.
- So…
there's one more thing I wanna say.
If people want to fight or argue,
I understand.
But everyone gets equal respect
once we sit at the table.
Can we all make that promise?
- Heck yeah.
- You bet.
- That's all I ask.
- Sure.
Yes.
- Okay?
- Okay!
- I promise!
- All right.
- Put your hands together.
- Okay.
- Everyone, dig in!
- Let's eat.
- Sounds good.
- Let's do this!
- Mmm, so good.
- Yeah, it's great.
I don't know how to make goya chanpuru.
You're from Okinawa, right?
It's an Okinawa thing.
Yeah, I'm the only one from Okinawa.
Oh, so do you make goya chanpuru a lot?
- Well, I don't even like goya.
- What?
- Really?
- You said that.
That's why I haven't touched it.
The hint of dried bonito flakes
is really nice.
- Oh, who else noticed?
- He's a foodie.
- Amazing.
- Oh, wow.
He knows his stuff.
It's crazy all ten of us are here.
Finally.
- Oh, she smiled!
- That was a nice little smirk.
She just take a shower?
Oh yeah, I couldn't dry my hair at all.
- Please, take a seat.
- Oh, there?
- That was so formal.
- Yeah, so polite.
- Please, madam.
- Such pretty features.
Her face is perfect.
So what do you think of the girls' room?
- It's super cute.
- Yeah.
And this is where we sleep.
It's gorgeous.
Wow, look at that!
- Really stylish.
- Right?
- Oh, hey, we were gonna ask--
- Where do you wanna sleep?
- Only the upper beds are open.
- Okay.
- The bed is up there.
- One is free.
Oh my god, that's cute.
So I'd just sleep up there?
This side is mine.
And this side is mine.
Oh, and over here we have
our little vanities.
Is this one open? Or this one?
- Here or here.
- So, here or here?
It's so elegant.
I know.
- Really cute.
- Yeah.
- It's nice, right?
All right, let's make a pact
to get along from now on.
What a rollercoaster!
Yeah. But it was nice to see
her smile at the end, wasn't it?
- It was nice.
- It did work out for the best.
It all turned out well. This isn't
a documentary about family, right?
Ah, no, it's not.
The way this season is going
it's starting to feel like…
- It's a reality dating show…
- a documentary about drama in a family.
- It's not a dating show!
- I know what you mean. I get it.
- They were fighting at the dinner table.
- It's not the same!
I can kind of understand
how the girls feel, but still…
you can kind of see how all of them
are bringing their different experiences
into the house.
So true.
So anyone could end up being
either the victim or the bully
depending on the situation.
But when problems like that come up,
it almost turns into
an After School Special.
It's a reality dating show. Don't forget.
It's not educational.
- It's not family drama?
- A mega-family.
I can tell you're struggling with this.
It's a reality dating show, guys.
We really saw them realize
that the dynamic can change on a dime.
Oh, yeah, that's interesting.
I think that's so important
for a group like this.
Oh, for sure.
You're right, and Rune said it
straight out, that was actually…
That was great. He's a real role model.
Definitely.
- What a guy. He's a model prisoner.
- A model prisoner!
Taka, he's not a prisoner.
No, listen.
This is a heartfelt family drama.
- It's not a family drama either, guys.
- Are you sure?
- Slow down.
- Rune is the overworked dad.
No, they're not all Rune's kids.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Let's go smoke.
So how is it?
What do you mean?
Like, how do you feel?
Now that we've got a new transfer student.
No, wait, I wanna hear
what it's like for you right now.
It's been a whirlwind.
Way more than I expected.
I mean, in terms of how things
have developed since we got here.
I haven't been able to process all of it.
But to be honest…
I don't think my feelings have changed.
Oh, really?
That's interesting,
'cause to shoot straight with you,
I thought she seemed like your type.
I mean…
The transfer student.
- Interesting.
- Yeah.
"Shoot straight with you?"
Is she in a western or something?
I feel like mostly old men say that.
- Or Dirty Harry.
- That's a weird way to put it.
- She seems like my type?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Um, I was really starting to feel unsure
about the whole thing actually.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
What do you mean by "unsure"?
I'm dying to know.
No, like, just-- Like, um…
I guess I…
I wasn't exactly jealous,
but maybe I was feeling
something close to that,
just to shoot straight with you.
She said it again.
Mmm, so, like,
that's why it was hard for me
to talk to you this way.
And when you asked me
to come out and smoke before,
my first thought was "eh, I don't know"
but yeah, I decided to come.
"I don't know" sounds bad to me.
Isn't that a bad sign?
Um, yeah, I just wasn't sure
if I'd be able to talk to you.
- Why?
- I was worried
that nothing I said would come out right
because of those jealous feelings.
That's why I was like,
"I don't know. It could be tough." Yeah.
- No, I get it.
- Mmm.
- Kazuma, let's go for a smoke.
- Oh, sure.
I mean, like…
Until now…
he hasn't really taken the lead, you know?
But he did in that situation.
I thought it was gross.
You mean, the whole thing with Mimi?
I got you.
Like, I get
that it's because they're friends.
Mmm-hmm.
I was interested in him,
he was, like, top choice for me.
But now he's…
- way down the list.
- He fell that far?
Yeah, I'm so much less interested in him.
- You're really pulling away from him, huh?
- It's crazy.
It happened so fast.
He's had you on his mind
the whole time, though.
- For real.
- Really?
Yeah. He kept saying, "Man, I need to talk
to Rinrin," like non-stop.
He did?
So why don't you try
talking to him, just once?
Hmm…
But you won't know
how he feels if you don't talk to him.
Then things are just gonna
stay like this with you guys.
Sure, you're right, but…
I think it'd be
a good idea to talk to him.
I don't know. I don't
really want to talk to him right now.
I feel like talking to him--
It makes me feel uncomfortable too,
when we still have, you know,
all this time together ahead of us here.
Yeah, you're right.
I don't think I'll approach him.
If he comes to me, I'll think about it.
Rinrin, can I talk to you?
- Oh, right on cue!
- He came!
That cool, Kazuma?
Of course.
Wow! Kazuma is such a nice guy!
Man, I really like Kazuma.
Thank you. Sorry.
So, Rinrin.
- Yeah, what?
- What're you mad about?
Was it how I escorted her?
I don't know if "escort" is the word.
Or was it the time
I invited her to sit down?
I'm trying to shoot straight with you,
I don't know why you're mad.
- "Shoot straight." You gotta be kidding.
- Is this some kind of prison slang?
Still don't think they're prisoners.
Look, from where I'm sitting,
the thing is…
When I told her that she should sit down,
I wasn't, you know, trying to make
a move on her or anything.
Like that wasn't it at all.
I mean I was just…
caught off guard
because a friend of mine showed up.
Um… how do I put this?
So what if she's your friend, dude?
I seriously couldn't care less.
Okay, fair enough.
Like, so what? You know?
Because, the fact is,
up until she came here,
you haven't really
been taking the lead at all.
But then suddenly you do it right away
when she's around. And I'm like, "wow."
It's kind of gross.
Guys like him
probably hate this kind of thing.
Hmm.
He's thinking,
"Oh, this girl's a handful."
But, that was just me,
um…
kind of…
I think I would've done the same thing
no matter who came.
I knew everyone
would give her the cold shoulder
'cause she's a transfer student.
And I thought it was a little rude
to make her stand there for so long.
So, since the seat next to me was open,
I told her to sit down.
That's just polite.
Well, I wanted to come out here
so I could apologize for making you
feel that way. I hope you understand.
I'm really sorry.
Hmm. Okay.
Sorry.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Mmm-hmm.
Good night.
Ooh, the plot thickens.
So true, so true.
I'm gonna shoot straight about--
Oh, man. Here we go, cowboy!
- Are we making this a thing?
- A hundred percent.
It's our official phrase.
Let's talk about the conversation
between Ryopi and Rinrin.
If I were in Rune's position,
I'd prefer it if she just
came out and said,
"I didn't like that you did that".
No attitude, just calm…
I might even feel flattered by that.
There's a chance that would
tug on your heartstrings.
I think all she needed to do
was let him know as clearly as she could
that she's been
focused on him this whole time.
That makes sense.
But remember, guys, Rinrin has been
cheated on like six times so far.
Oh, so she has trauma.
So naturally she might be
a little more sensitive
about that than most people.
What Ryopi did
doesn't count as cheating, right?
I guess she can't help imagining
the worst-case scenario
of where that could lead.
Let's pick which guy
Mimi should fall in love with
so that everything works out for the best.
Oh, yeah! Perfect!
- That's one way to resolve this.
- Let's see.
Who would be a good target?
It's not gonna be Maru, right?
- Right.
- Ayacheru would be crushed.
Kazuma.
Kazuma!
It's gotta be him. He's the best bet.
Quite messing around!
You can't say Kazuma, okay?
You're the producer!